Hey, Carl. Here's a postcard from Nina.
Hey,Carl. 这是一张明信片 来自于Nina.
From Prague.
来自于布拉格.
I saw Nina here two minutes ago.
我看到Nina在这儿 两分钟前.
Oh, they've been back for days.
Oh, 她们已经回来好几天了.
She writes,"I miss my baby, but I'm glad I'm here."
她写道, "我想念我的孩子, 但是我很高兴我在这里."
What else?
还有什么?
She says they've just arrived.
她说她们刚刚到达.
Boy, this took a long time to get here.
Boy,这个花了很长时间才寄到.
She says it's beautiful and she's already in love with the city.
她说那儿很美 并且她已经爱上了那座城市.
I've never been.
我从来没去过.
Me, neither. She makes it sound great.
我也没有. 她让那里听起来很棒.
She said they had done a lot of walking.
她说她们做了许多步行.
And she was going to do a lot more walking when she got back.
并且她打算做更多步行 在她回来之后.
Let's see. It's a funny thing about travel.
咱们看看, 它是件奇怪的事情 关于旅行.
What?
什么?
People go all that way, to a completely new place.
人们走那么远, 到一个完全陌生的地方.
They see their lives from a new perspective,
他们从一个新的角度去看他们的生活.
-you know?   -Sure
-你知道吗?   -当然
And they make decisions...
并且他们做决定…
like they're going to do a lot more walking.
像他们将做更多步行
Travel's a funny thing.
旅行是件有趣的事.
Have a good trip, sir.
祝你旅途愉快, 先生.